[{
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Staff development is an ongoing process aimed at enhancing both the professional and personal growth of an organizationâ€™s employees, especially those in roles.",
    "answer": "managerial"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "The objective of staff development is to ensure long-term growth by cultivating attributes such as improved , knowledge acquisition, and refined decision-making abilities.",
    "answer": "attitudes"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "In the modern business environment, investing in staff development creates a continuous culture that promotes adaptability, , and high-level performance.",
    "answer": "innovation"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Effective staff development aligns individual growth with organizational goals, ensuring that employees grow while the company benefits from a workforce.",
    "answer": "motivated"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "The process of staff development involves several stages that guide both the organization and the employees through growth and improvement. One of these steps is identifying the current and future development of both the organization and its staff.",
    "answer": "needs"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Once development needs are identified, organizations must evaluate the skills, performance, and potential of existing managers through processes like performance reviews.",
    "answer": "appraisal"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "An important step in staff development is preparing a detailed of an organization's current staffing levels and future needs.",
    "answer": "inventory"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "After identifying strengths and weaknesses, organizations design tailored development programs to address those deficiencies. These programs may include on-the-job training, workshops, mentoring, or other activities.",
    "answer": "development"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "The actual implementation of training and development activities involves delivering programs either in-house or through external agencies, ensuring employees can engage in the training effectively.",
    "answer": "conducting"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "The final step in staff development is to evaluate the effectiveness of the programs by measuring , gathering feedback, tracking career progression, and identifying areas for improvement.",
    "answer": "behavioral changes"
  }
]
